那今天Meyer副总统很有压力咯 Rod?
So Vice President Meyer is under pressure today, Rod.
说得对 Vic 她因为人家冲她笑
That's right, Vic. She fired one of her
就炒掉了一名特勤工作人员
secret service men because he smiled.
他不是被炒了 是调动了
He wasn't fired, he was reassigned.
这对副总统的幕僚长 Amy Brookheimer来说面子上可不好看
This doesn't look good for the VP's chief of staff Amy Brookheimer.
Amy 你现在听的是Crock频道么?
Amy, you listening to Crock FM right now?
是的 我正在听呢
Yeah, that's exactly what I'm doing.
呃 先别慌 我还有些手段
Well, don't sweat it. I can still bust some moves in this town.
手段? 不是吧 Mike?
Bust some moves? Really, Mike?
我是Mike拳道的黑带高手
I have a black belt in Mike Kwan Do.
好了 先生 不行
All right, sir, no.
好吧 好吧 小心点 面点男
Okay, okay. Hey, hey, easy, dough boy.
把手从我衣服上拿开!
Hands off the suit.
那就怪我吧 Brookheimer
Uh-oh, blame me Brookheimer.
不许笑了 Vic 那可是叛国!
Stop laughing there, Vic. That's treason.
喂?
Hello? - Dan.
你看到Amy出糗都高兴得硬了吧?
You must have a huge schadenboner over this Amy flack.
我对我同事如此公然血腥...
Oh, I take no pleasure in my colleague's very public, brutal...
我这要看电视呢 你能挪一下吗?
I'm trying to watch TV. Would you please move?
而且有可能是事业终点的受辱 完全不感到高兴 Jonah
And probably career-ending humiliation, Jonah.
天 她这回肯定要爆发大姨妈了
God, she is gonna go ape-shit menstrual over this.
嘿 我这正和电信公司打电话呢 你能别在那嚷嚷大姨妈么?
Hey, I'm on the phone with AT&T. Can you stop shouting menstrual?
是啊 她可能会有点大姨妈来了的感觉
Yeah, you know, she'll probably go a little menstrual.
她可能会的 但是你仔细一想的话
Yeah, she probably will. Although, when you think about it,
这个对你来说不利 是吗?
- it's actually kind of worse for you. - Is that right?
嗯 副总统办公室一直不停地出事
Well, the VP'S office is a cataclysm on spin cycle.
而且你们还有怀孕流言满天飞
And then you got that pregnancy rumor flying around
一些乱七八糟的
like the contents of a broken fucking condom.
这一条肯定是最先爆出来的 你已经是活死人了...搞毛啊?
It's gonna be last in and first out and you're a dead Dan walk... what the fuck?
这玩意太脏了得跟碗一起洗
This is going in with the dirty dishes, man.
天哪 要是弄坏了的话 我就算在你丫的房租里!
For fuck's sake. If this is broken, I'm adding it to your fucking rent.
请拨打热线参与话题 Amy Brookheimer应否离开?
Please call in on this one. Should Amy Brookheimer go?
重点是 你们搞好治安
But the bottom line is, you keep the streets safe,
我就搞定你们的预算
I'll keep your budget safe.
呃 我本来想说这让我喜笑颜开的
Well, I was gonna say that brings a smile to my face,
不过这就不安全了 对吧女士?
but that would be safe, wouldn't it, ma'am?
这个好笑 Bill 你被炒了
That's very funny, Bill. You're fired.
我开玩笑的 开玩笑的 开玩笑的
I'm kidding. I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
女士 该走了
Hey, ma'am, it's leave o'clock.
好的 我恐怕要离席了 先生们
Okay, yes. I'm afraid I have to go, gentlemen.
Mike 这可不是故事
Mike, this is not a story.
Collins对我做了几个表情 然后就调他走了
Collins made a bunch of faces, he was reassigned.
这就不应该上新闻 这到底怎么捅出去的?
That shouldn't be news. How in the hell did this happen?
这他妈可是特勤处啊
It's the secret service, for Christ's sake.
特勤处的特就是说要闭嘴的意思
Secret as in shut the fuck up.
特勤的意思就是说给我工作 好吗?
And service as in you work for me, okay?
那你为什么不闭上你的鸟嘴?
So why don't you shut the fuck up?
我们有一个死敌 我要知道他是谁
We have an enemy and I want a name
然后往死里问他要答案
and a severed head that answers to that name,
如果他还能说话的话
or would if it could still talk.
好了 我要进办公室了
All right, I'm gonna be in my office.
不带你们!
Alone!
噢 Gary 副总统
Ooh, Gary, did the veep
是不是边骂边把门摔你脸上了?
just bitch-slap you with a door?
她不是有心的 她今天脑子里的事太多了
She didn't mean that. She's got a lot on her mind today.
对 你是说要炒Amy之类的么?
Oh, yeah, you mean like firing Amy?
还是说要炒某些私下和Macauley搞关系 来破坏总统事情的人呢
Or someone who's undermining the president by back-channeling Macauley.
一派胡言 好吧 我要告诉你们一些事
- That's bullshit. - Okay, I need to tell you guys something.
什么 是她的无水洗手液又用完了么?
Oh, what, is she out of hand sanitizer again?
我不能说 我不能告诉你们
I can't say this. I can't tell you this.
Gary 你为什么话只说一半?
Gary, why are you talking in cliffhangers?
Selina流产了
Selina's had a miscarriage.
呃 这对我们来说是好事
Well, this is good for us.
干得好啊 Dandroid 她怎么样了?
- Nicely done, Dandroid. - How is she?
我会说是从他妈的政治困境中解脱了
Free from a major fucking political headache, I'd say.
你这也太冷了吧 Dan
That's deep space cold, Dan.
请问你为什么尿的是液氮啊?(温度极低)
Explains why you piss liquid nitrogen.
好的 Ted 我回头打给你
Okay, Ted. I'll call you back, then.
那就是...
So that's...
什么? 发生什么事了?
What? What's going on?
呃 我跟大家说我新买的割草机呢
Uh, I was telling the guys about my riding mower I got.
哇 Gary
Wow, Gary.
这通电话可够短的 你看
That was quick. Look at that.
好了 同志们 进我办公室来吧
Okay, everybody. Please come into my office.
白宫代表来了 大家一起说喂哦
White House is in the house. * Everybody say way-o! *
屎天大楼出现了
The skyscraper of shit has arrived.
副总统女士 今天的头条
Madam Vice President, top story today
是病毒视频席卷全国
is that viral sensation that's sweeping the nation.
你说什么呢?
What are you talking about?
我能进来么? 不 你不能
- May I? - No, you may not.
好吧
Okay.
这个视频的名字叫出卖Seline
It's tagged Selina Sell-Outta.
Selina Meyer 副总统失控了么?
Selina Meyer, has this veep lost control?
呃 呃 呃 她声称是个环保主义者
- Are, are, are. - She says she's an environmentalist,
可她却否决了环境保护的议案
but she vetoes environmental protection.
她发起的绿色产业委员会里
She sets up a clean jobs task force
不止有一位 而是两位石油界人士
that includes not one, but two oil men.
我来告诉你真相
I'm gonna tell you the truth.
到底副总统的脑子是什么状态
What is the mental state of a veep
才能为了微笑而炒掉一个人?
that fires a man for smiling?
这一段我最喜欢了 你能...
I love this part. - Could you...
我是Selina Meyer
I am Selina Meyer.
我完全不知道我办公室里发生了什么事
And I don't have any idea what's going on in my office.
好吧 把你的断腿收起来赶紧滚吧 Jonah
All right, pack up your limbs and get the fuck out, Jonah.
把他赶出去 嘿 别怪报信的人啊
- Get him out. - Hey, don't shoot the messenger.
我能上手吗? 你没有机会打过我的
- Is punching allowed? - Oh, you wouldn't stand a chance.
我手比你长多了
I have a much longer reach.
大家都看过这个了么? 没有!
- Did everybody get a chance to see this? - No!
我们怎么止损?
I mean, how are we gonna shut this negativity down?
Amy 我们要怎么办? 呃 这不准确
- Amy, what are we gonna do? - Yeah, well, it's inaccurate.
技术上来说 特勤处的那个人是调走了
Technically, the secret service guy was reassigned.
就是 而且技术上来说我们也没有 放两个石油界的人
Yeah, and technically we didn't put two oil guys
在绿色产业委员会里 那我懂了
- on clean jobs task force. - Oh, yeah, I see.
技术上来说这个办公室也运作流畅着呢
And technically this is a fully functioning office, too.
嗯 那个特勤处的小丑肯定爆了我们的料
Well, that secret service clown has obviously leaked us.
说得对 Mike 很好
That's right, Mike. Good. You know what?
你得去和他谈谈 好吗?
You're gonna have to go talk to him, okay?
你是现在我们这个办公室里最接近正常的人了
You are the closest to normal we've got going in this office right now.
谢谢 我觉得
Thanks, I think.
好了 白宫发了一个要求
Okay, there's a White House request to publish
说要公布所有特勤处工作人员的记录
all the secret service office personnel records.
你玩我呢吧? 他们现在就要我们的记录?
Are you kidding me? They want our records now?
我们怎么办? 怎么办?
What are we gonna do? What?
呃 我们必须公布那些材料
Well, we have to release those. And that has got me thinking
那我们为什么不干脆把所有记录都公布了呢?
why not release all of our fucking records?
彻底解决这件事 你是说真的么?
full disclosure. - are you serious?
对 公布所有的东西
Yeah, publish everything.
所有的邮件 所有的电话记录
All of our emails, all of our phone records.
好的 好的 这样他们就没有时间仔细看了
Right, right, 'cause they won't have time to read everything.
我是说 你总不能什么都看
I mean, you can't read everything.
我应该看的东西有一半都没看过
I don't read half the stuff I'm supposed to.
那就是说我们显得什么都不藏着掖着
So by showing that we have nothing to hide,
可事实上却可以隐瞒一些东西
then we can actually hide some stuff.
Dan 你觉得呢?
Dan, what do you think about this?
我只是觉得这个事情可能会把我们都搞废了
I just think that this could blow up in all of our faces.
你不能因为不是你家孩子就...
Just because this isn't your baby, you don't...
天哪 真对不起 噢 没事的 没事的
- God, I am so sorry. - Oh, it's fine. It's fine.
这就像加强版大姨妈一样 别担心
I mean, it was like a heavy period. Don't worry about it.
好吧 你们知道吗? 我们就这么干!
All right, you know what, guys? We're doing this.
我决定我们
I've made the decision that we are going to
公开所有的通讯文件
release all of our correspondence.
现在玩的就是大结局
Full disclosure is now the name of the game.
Mike会给你交待剩下的细节
Mike will fill you in on the rest of it.
是吧 Mike? 是的 女士
- Right, Mike? - Yes, ma'am.
好的 谢谢
Okay. Thank you.
好了 这显然不会彻底解决的
All right, obviously it is not gonna be full disclosure.
这也就差不多解决一下
Okay? It's gonna be partial disclosure light.
我们不能有书面记录
We don't want to have a paper trail
关于绿色产业的
on clean jobs.
也不能有...你是在做记录么?
There can be no... Are you writing that down?
你为什么要写下来?
Why would you be writing that down?
任何涉及Sidney Purcell 和绿色产业的东西都不能有
Nothing about Sidney Purcell having access to clean jobs, all right?
我们得查查Sue的日历 保证
We have to check Sue's calendar, make sure
会议记录靠谱
there are no meetings there that I did-didn't have.
那本偶然出现的种族歧视小册子也得销毁
The accidentally racist brochure that we had to shred.
那个当然是要重新编过
Oh, we're gonna redact that for sure.
不过吧 我还是觉得
But the thing is, is that I still think
里面应该有点料才行
there needs to be something embarrassing in there.
你们懂我意思吧? 当然
you know What I mean? - Sure.
这样的话别人不会觉得我们是事前清理过了的
So it doesn't look as if we've just airbrushed
对 这个想法很好 很好
the nipples out of this fucking thing.
稍微处理一下起居记录
No, that's really good. And it makes... yeah.
媒体们就喜欢那种东西
Massages at the residence. The press will obsess about those.
处理? 怎么处理? 你背上的面膜
Massages? What Massages? - your back facials.
噢 背上的面膜? 什么东西?
Oh. - back facials? What?
对 我背上长痘痘了 背痘
Yeah, I get back acne. Backne.
好吧 这个我觉得问题不大
Okay, okay. I think we can live with that.
那我们要公布起居日志么?
Shall we release the logs from the residence?
好的 当然 这个可以公布
Uh, yeah, sure. We can do that.
好了吗? 好了
Okay? - Okay.
开始行动 噢 Dan
Got a plan. Oh, Dan.
我能跟你说一下吗?
Can I talk to you just for a quick sec?
是 你要我留下么?
Yeah. - you want me to stay?
我叫你留下了吗?
Did I ask you to stay?
谢谢
Thank you.
呃 Dan 听着 有什么事需要我担心么?
Um, Dan, listen, do I have anything that I need to be worried about?
随便举个例子哈
Just a random example might be
比方说关于Macauley修正案什么的...
anything about the Macauley amendment you need...
不 不用 女士 不用么?
- No. No, ma'am. - No?
如果这间办公室里任何人和那个
Because if anyone thought this office
违背总统愿望
had anything to do with that amendment,
和政策的修正案有瓜葛的话
which went against the president's wishes and policy,
这就完全不对头了哦
that would be completely wrong
而且这会牵扯所有人
and it would be curtains for everyone.
是的 女士
Yes, ma'am.
我是说 我不知道你做了还是没做什么
I mean, I don't know what you did or didn't do,
但是我知道我不能知道
but I do know that I can't know
你知道或者不知道什么
what you know or you don't know.
你的明白? 我懂的
you know? - I know.
好的 很好
Okay, good.
我去!
Oh, fuck.
你没事吧 女士?
Uh, you okay, ma'am?
没事 Ame 听着
Yeah, Ame, listen.
很抱歉我刚才让你吃瘪了
I'm sorry I snapped at you there.
我以为你会炒了我
I thought you were about to fire me.
很遗憾知道你失去了...
I'm sorry to hear
你不再怀着孕了
that you lost... that you're no longer pregnant.
是的 谢谢
Oh, yeah, thanks.
事情是这样
Um, here's the deal, though.
别的先不说
On top of everything else,
我想Ted要甩了我
I think that Ted is getting ready to dump me.
你那个...
What is that...
点头是什么意思?
nodding thing supposed to mean?
不 没有 我…
No, no, my...
是在处理信息
processing information.
点头代表我在缓冲哈
The nod of my head is like I'm buffering.
好吧 那你缓冲完成之后
Oh, well, once you're done buffering,
你在想什么呢?
what is it that you're thinking?
我不知道 也许震惊已经过去了
I don't know. Maybe the thrill is gone.
你什么意思?
What do you mean?
就是说听到这个事情的震惊
Like the thrill of the whole power thing wore off.
现在他就不像是...
And now he just doesn't like what's un...
不像什么?
Doesn't like what?
他就是不...不是...
He just doesn't... doesn't really...
好吧 我想你最好是从我办公室出去吧
Okay, I think you'd better get out of my office.
我的意思不是... 没关系的
- See, I didn't mean that... - It's okay.
没事 好的
- It's fine. - Okay.
你就...
Just...
我看看
Let me see this.
你看 我还能认出来这个名字好吗?
Look, I can still read the names, okay?
你得用记号笔把整个词划满
You've got to put black marker over all the words.
Abby 你整晚
Abby, you may have to pull an all-nighter
都得重写IDGN编号
with the IDGN number redacting
如果你重写IDGN编号的进度跟不上的话
if you're behind on the IDGN number redacting.
好了 同志们 12个小时 我们一定要达成目标
Okay, folks, 12 hours. Let's make it happen.
我们可以的
We can do this.
我会捡起来的
I'll get it.
谢谢你们这么短的时间就能赶来
Thank you all for coming on such short notice.
我明白 谁知道透明政府
I know, who'd have thought transparent government
会占据你这么多的视野呢?
would take up so much of your field of vision?
你们看吧
Have at it.
趁热哦 你拿得了吗?
- Get it while it's hot. - You got that?
你还好吧?
You good?
给我来点咖啡 天 我太需要它了
Cup of joe for the guys. Man, I need it.
我马上就能晕过去
I could pass out right now.
你说是有关国家安全的事
You said this was a homeland security issue.
确实是的 这就是国家安全角度...的事情
It's exactly that. It's a very homeland security angle... issue.
所以我迫切的要来这里
It's imperative to me being here.
你上过火线么 Mike?
You ever been in the line of fire, Mike?
是的 先生 和副总统一起去过伊拉克
Yes, sir. Went to Iraq with the veep.
去展示感恩节火鸡
Presented a Thanksgiving turkey.
我也在 我可不记得有开火
I was there. No fire as I recall.
不 但是火线的线在那里
No, but the line was there.
你要说吗?
Whew. Do you mind?
你在阿灵顿公墓干得怎么样? (美国军人公墓)
So how's the place been over at Arlington Cemetery going?
我听说那挺好的 那里没有什么好笑的
- I hear it's pretty nice there. - It's nothing to smile about.
我还照顾着我的叔叔 他有老年痴呆
I'm also looking after my uncle. He has dementia.
他没说什么好笑的东西么?
Does he ever say anything funny?
你想要什么 McLintock先生?
What do you want, Mr. McLintock?
只是看看你过得好不好 Martin
Just want to make sure you're doing okay, Martin.
你以为是我告密的
You think I'm the whistle-blower.
告密听起来太爱国了
Whistle-blowing makes it sound patriotic.
我他妈就莫名其妙的被调走了
I was fucking transferred for nothing.
不 你是因为太爱笑太随便而被调走的
No, you were transferred for being jocular and overfamiliar.
安保人员就应该像墙纸一样
Security guys are supposed to be like wallpaper.
而不是像猩猩一样笑嘻嘻的
They're not supposed to be grinning like some ape.
好的
Okay.
时代周刊说我们是为了隐藏一些事情
The Times are saying we're trying to hide stuff
开闸放水
by causing a deluge.
他们管这个叫电子海啸
They're calling it an e-nami.
有人说那个背部面膜的事么?
Is anybody picking up on the back facials?
媒体不是应该找那些背部面膜的事么?.
The press was supposed to pick on those damn back facials.
没有 嘿 给我说一个J!
- No. - Hey, gimme a J!
大家好啊
Hi, everybody.
没有人道歉么?
So no apologies?
道什么歉?
For what?
噢 道什么歉?
Oh, for what? Oh.
华盛顿邮报 第17版
Washington Post. Page 17.
你们公布了一封关于给一位不具名白宫助手
You've disclosed an email containing birthday gift
生日礼物建议的电子邮件
suggestions for an unnamed White House aide.
建议一...
Suggestion number one...
老二形状的蛋糕
A cake in the shape of a dick.
建议二...
Suggestion number two... A smart new hat
老二形状的新帽子 噢 这一条被发掘了!
- in the shape of a dick. - Oh, that made it in there!
所有人都知道这是我
Everybody knows this is me, guys.
所有人? 真的么? 是的 所有人
- Oh, everybody? Really? - Yes, everybody.
白宫可是有3000位工作人员啊 Jonah
There are 3,000 people on the White House payroll, Jonah.
可谁是副总统联络官呢 Amy?
Who's the VP liaison, Amy?
我去咖啡店的时候 我去开会的时候
I'm going into coffee shops, I'm going into meetings,
人们看着我就会互相耳语
and people are looking at me and whispering.
他们耳语的内容就是老二蛋糕!
And they are whispering Dick Cake.
我是西翼之Jonah
West Wing, Jonah.
不是 DC是谁?
No, who is DC?
呃 老二蛋糕
Uh, Dick Cake.
我勒个大艹 是Ryan吗?
Oh, for fuck's sake. Is this Ryan?
噢 不 不 不! 怎么了?
- Oh, no, no, no! - What?
每次Ted来过夜的的记录都被挖出来了
Every time Ted stayed overnight at the residence
Ted肯定会喜欢的
- has been fully disclosed. - Oh, Ted's gonna love that.
有一些博客把Ted的过夜记录 和怀孕传言联系起来了
Some of the bloggers are linking Ted's overnighters to the pregnancy rumors.
什么? 不是吧
What? Oh, come on.
Mike 你能让我没怀过孕么?
Mike, can't you make me not have been pregnant?
天哪! 看见了吧?
- God! - You see?
这就是说出真相的代价 完全没有好处
This is what happens when you tell the truth. Nothing good comes of it.
好了 我给你来一杯玫瑰茶
Okay, I'm gonna get you a cup of rose hip tea.
路透社的Keith报道了特勤处的事 现在曝光了
Keith at Reuters says secret service story, it's out there.
现在? 是的
Right now? - Yeah.
看起来副总统办公室因为
It seems the veep's office has compounded the problem
侮辱当事人为猩猩而把问题搞得更严重了
by insulting the man and calling him an ape.
谁应该对这个疯狂的事件负责呢?
Who's responsible for this deranged campaign?
是新闻官Mike McLintock?
Mike McLintock, press officer?
是幕僚长Amy Brookheimer 还是Selina Meyer本人呢?
Chief of staff Amy Brookheimer, or Selina Meyer herself?
当然了 她对此负有终极责任
Of course, she bears ultimate responsibility.
总统不会喜欢这个的
Potus will not like this.
这肯定会让总统那边崩溃的
This is gonna cause a total potal meltdown.
好了 把他弄出去 Dan
All right, get him out of here, Dan.
你怎么不跑过去看看你能不能嘬你自己的蛋糕呢?
Yeah, why don't you run along and see if you can suck your own cake?
这个段子有内涵 Dan
Oh, that's clever, Dan.
是你说的么 Mike?
Did you say those things, Mike?
表现太好了 大文豪 真的
Ace play, Shakespeare. Really.
你居然骂一个老兵叫猩猩
When in doubt, call a vet an ape.
你到底是走了什么后门才得到这份工作的啊?
Remind me, who did you blackmail to get this job?
好了 现在马上进办公室
All right, you know what? Let's get in my office right now.
您的茶就快好了 谢谢
your tea is almost ready. - Thank you.
又一次了 我们见证了这个办公室
Yet again we find ourselves in an office
有多他妈无能
that is completely non-fucking-functioning.
现在我们要怎么办
So what are we gonna do?
没错 我们要炒个人
Exactly. We are gonna fire someone.
很好 你们有更好的主意吗
That's right. Does anybody have a better idea?
那...
All right, so...
炒谁呢
Who is it gonna be, huh?
Sue 噢 Sue
- Sue. - Oh, Sue.
真好笑
That's funny, you guys.
不过说实话 Sue还不够重要
But seriously, Sue's not important enough.
那谁重要呢
Who is?
哦 我知道了
Oh, I know.
你们三个就挺重要的
You three are important enough.
女士 我承诺会尽我所能
Ma'am, I just want to say I promise to do everything I can
来修补Amy漏洞层出的政策
to fix Amy's botched full disclosure policy
和Mike的信口开河
and Mike's security blunder.
嘿 拍马屁是修补不了嗝儿屁的  Dan
Hey, suck-up isn't gonna fix a fuck-up, Dan.
知道吗 你没有豁免权
All right? You're not exempt.
Gary 嗯?
Gary. - Hmm?
我要找一个非常隐秘的地方
I need some sort of a discreet place
跟Ted见个面
where I can have a rendezvous with Ted, please.
不能有人打扰 好的 女士
- Where nobody goes. - Yes, ma'am.
谢谢 好了
Thank you. All right.
你们现在可以出去了
You may leave my office now.
关门吗 当然关
- Shut? - Of course shut!
哦 天呐
Oh, lord.
哦 你有没有放一点儿...
Ooh, did you put a dash of...
蜂蜜在玫瑰果里 放了 女士
Honey in the rose hip? Yes, ma'am.
我还放了块Fig Newton在旁边 (饼干品牌)
I put a little Fig Newton there for you as well.
噢 太棒了 Gary 是
- Oh, outstanding, Gary. - Yeah.
干嘛 好吧 对于造成的不便我很抱歉
What? Okay, I'm sorry for the inconvenience.
我明白
another one. - I understand.
新闻界追得我屁滚尿流 哦 那挺好
- Press is up my ass. - Oh, so, okay, great.
现在你能感受到我有多苦逼了
Then you know exactly what my world is like.
你放屁 我又没有个Mike Amy或他妈的Dan在身边
No, bullshit. I don't have a Mike, an Amy, or fucking Dan.
你想要他们吗 那就拿走
Oh, do you want them? You can have them.
我他妈现在就能把他们仨打包送你 只要你想要
I'll give you a fucking deal on all three of them, too, if you want.
你的待人之道可真好
That's a nice way to treat people.
这是我现在的真实感觉 水来了
- Well, that's how I feel. - Here we go.
你不用这么烦躁
You don't have to be snarky about this.
我操你妈
Oh, my fucking lord!
你真的要冷静 好吧
You really need to calm down, okay?
你要尊重Gary的东西
You need to respect Gary's stuff here.
对不起 Gary 没关系
- Sorry, Gary. - That's okay.
我他妈这是私人生活
Look, this is my fucking private life.
我知道 我以为我是私底下干你的
- No, I know. - I thought I was fucking you in private.
Ted 不要这样 我喜欢私底下干你
Ted, come on. I love to fuck you in private.
嘿 听着 谢谢你给我回电话
Hey, you know what? Thanks for returning my call.
我能给的消息就是 请你他妈别再打老子电话了
The message was, please don't fucking call me again.
所以你干嘛不带上你的鸟嘴
So why don't you just take your beak and shove it up
找个死尸的屁股塞进去 干你娘的
some corpse's ass, okay, you vulture motherfucker?
不会是记者吧 是
Was that a journalist? - Yes.
我的老天爷啊 怎么了
- Oh, God! - What?
你这是干嘛 Ted 你不能让他去干他娘
What are you doing, Ted? You can't tell him to fuck his mother.
实际上 是她娘 有什么区别
- Her mother, actually. - What the hell?
她们... 拜托 动点脑子
- They... - Come on, use your head.
你这是在使事情恶化 冷静点
You're just making it worse. Get yourself together.
Selina 我要去透气
Selina, I need some air.
我们待会要谈谈
And we need to talk.
呃 Gary?
Uh, Gary?
是的 女士
Yes, ma'am?
我要走了 好的 好的
- I'm gonna go. - Okay. Okay.
我要你留在这儿 好的
I want you to stay here. - Okay.
我要你跟Ted做个了结
I need you to end it with Ted.
好的 什么 是的 我要你让他走
- Okay. What? - Yeah, I want you to let him go.
但你要做得很感性
But you need to do it very sensitively.
确定不会有任何影响
And just make sure there aren't any repercussions
或者之类的东西出现 知道吗
or anything like that, okay?
呃 恕我直言 女士
Um, with all due respect, ma'am,
如果你去说会不会好一点
wouldn't it be better if it came from you?
嗯 不会 不行吗
- Mmm, uh-uh. - No?
不行 因为我不能再冒险跟他谈了
No, because I can't run the risk of talking to him again
我觉得他会要甩掉我
because I think that he is about to dump me.
所以我不想被别人甩
So I'm not gonna be the dumpee.
我要甩别人
I'm gonna be the dumper.
好吧 他才是被甩的那个
Okay? He's gonna be the dumpee.
所以 要你来做 好吧
So, you've got to go do that.
好的
Okay.
好的 好的
Okay. Okay.
噢 你房子真不错
Oh, um, your house is so nice.
谢谢 非常感谢
Oh, thank you. Thank you so much.
您这样说真贴心
It's really sweet for you to say that.
好
Okay.
她还是会生气的 对不对 是
- She can go off, can't she? - Yeah.
刚才对不起了 没关系
- Yeah, sorry about that. - That's okay.
没关系
That's okay.
也许这也算件好事
So maybe it's a good thing.
什么 什么好事
What? What's a good thing?
她再也不想见你了
That she doesn't want to see you anymore.
女士 你消失一个多小时了
Oh, ma'am. You've been off radar for over an hour.
我错过什么了没
Oh, did I miss anything?
总统骑着狮子穿过去了还是什么
Did the president ride through on a lion or something?
不 但你要去303博彩协会露个脸
No, but you need to do a drop-in on the Gaming Association in 303.
好吧 我可不想最后沦落到 抱着马头入睡
All right. I don't want to end up with a horse's head in my bed.
虽然现在枕头上确实有这个空间
Though there's room for one now.
真想知道
I just want to know.
我真心希望你是第一个知道的
I hope you find out first. I really do.
嘿 你知道吗 我要是被炒了 那就是很他妈大件事
Hey, you know what? I get fired, it's a big fucking deal.
炒了你还能当是提前退休
For you, it's early retirement.
啊 真有趣
Ah, that was fun.
刚有个资深律师把我的院子完全毁了
I just had a senior attorney completely trash my yard.
你还好吧 我帮你冲杯咖啡
- You okay? - Yeah, let me get you some coffee.
怎么了 兄弟 你要不要跟我谈谈
What happened, buddy? You want to talk about it?
他完完全全毁了它 我还怕他会不会切了我的...
He completely tore it up. I was afraid he was gonna cut my...
等等 你刚是不是叫我兄弟了
Wait a second. Did you just call me buddy?
你们不听我说话的 你们从来都不会听我说话 发生什么事了
You don't listen to me. You never listen to me. What's going on?
没事 你们想从我这套东西
Nothing. - you want something from me.
你们想要我说是谁要被炒了
You want me to tell you who's getting fired.
拜托 我们就想知道她在想什么
Come on, we just want to know what she's thinking.
我什么都不会说的
I'm not gonna tell you anything.
这样 忘掉细节问题
All right, you know what? Forget about the specifics.
我们就当这儿有个女农场主
Let's pretend there's a female farmer
她养了一只马 一只羊和一只猪
and she's got a horse, a sheep, and a pig, okay?
她会丢掉哪个
Who does she get rid of?
猪
The pig.
妈的 等等 谁是猪
Shit. Wait. Who is that?
拜托 自己想嘛
Oh, come on. Work it out.
我干嘛要帮你们
Why should I help you guys?
Gary 副总统要吃午餐 就来
- Gary, veep needs her lunch. - I'm on it.
我宁愿当猪 也不想做骑着高马的死猴子
I'd rather be a pig than an ass-monkey up on his high horse.
看 这三种动物适合你
There, that's three animals for you.
你刚是不是悄悄贴过来了
Did you just sidle?
我从来没见过你这样
I don't think I've ever seen you sidle.
是这样 Selina要炒个人
Look, Selina wants to fire somebody.
很明显 我不希望是我
Obviously, I don't want it to be me.
但说实话 我也不希望是你
But honestly, I don't want it to be you.
继续 我很期待你说服我
Oh, go on. Looking forward to you selling this one to me.
我们得达成自杀合约
We should form a suicide pact. All right?
如果她要炒我 你就走 反之亦然
If she tries to fire me, you walk and vice versa.
她不会同时炒我们俩个
She's not gonna fire both of us.
这样太有危机感了
That would look like a crisis.
因此 我们俩个她都不会炒
Therefore, she can fire neither of us.
我只有一个条件...我要先看着你死
One condition... I watch you die first
再反复捅你来确认
and I get to stab you repeatedly to make sure.
McLintock也要参加自杀合约
McLintock wants in on the suicide pact.
什么 是的 经典的一步
What? - Yeah. a classic move.
我九十年代也用过这招
I did one of these back in the '90s
为Hartigan议员工作时
when I worked for congressman Hartigan.
干嘛要让你跟我们一起自杀合约
Why would we let you in on our suicide pact?
因为三个比两个要好
Because three is better than two.
如果是睾丸那就不一定了
Not with testicles.
我看到了一封小电子邮件
I came across a little email
是你写给Macauley的幕僚长的
from you to Macauley's chief of staff.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
你不知道那电邮吗 基本能确认
You don't know about an email that basically confirms
你跟Macauley参议员有私交呢
you had talks with Senator Macauley?
那电邮写了些什么
What exactly did this email say?
哦 就是些
Oh, just something like,
参议员说 谢谢你 伙计
the senator says, 'thanks, buddy.'
这罪名很难成立
Well, that's hardly incriminating.
来源处应该还会有更多证据吧
There's probably more where that came from.
我很能编的
I'm getting really good at dacting.
你是指不胡编乱造吗
Do you mean un-redacting?
洗去污点 对 对
- Taking the black off. - Yeah, yeah.
嘿 这白痴可以跟我们自杀合约的
Hey, so goofball here can get in on the suicide pact.
棒 越多越好
Well, great. The more the merrier.
组团自杀
Team Suicide.
你那个Hartigan自杀合约最后怎样了
So what happened with your Hartigan suicide pact?
哦 我们集体被炒了
Oh, we got fired.
好了 小猫咪们 浸猪笼时间到 来吧
Okay, kittens. Time to get drowned. Let's go.
女士 好
- Ma'am. - Yeah.
Gary 今天午餐时间 你跟Selina去了哪
Gary, where were you and Selina at lunchtime today?
我家 这不符合规章制度
- We were at my place. - That's not protocol.
我们就是这种关系 不要羡慕嫉妒恨哦 Sue
Don't be jealous that we've taken that step, Sue.
我跟她的关系更亲密
I'm closer to her than you are.
什么
What?
Gary 这不是比赛
Gary, this is not a competition.
晚了 她穿几号鞋
Too late. What's her shoe size?
七号 七号半
Seven. - Seven And a half.
好吧 她最不想看到的两个堂亲戚是谁
Okay, who are the two cousins she never wants to see?
Beverly和Michael
Beverly and Michael.
走狗屎运 事实在这里 Sue
- Oh, got lucky there. - Here's the deal, Sue.
你不会赢的 知道吗
You can't win, all right?
我是绝对可靠的 了解么
Basically, I'm infallible, okay?
比如带着工作证去帮副总统买验孕棒吗
Like when you bought pregnancy tests for the veep wearing your staff ID?
这样可靠吗 Gary
Infallible like that, Gary?
Gary 华盛顿邮报一个员工告诉我的
Gary, look, a staffer at the Post told me.
药店那个人看见了你的证 说给了媒体听
The guy at the drugstore saw the badge and sold the story.
对不起 Gary
Sorry, Gary.
也就是说 只要一个人走了 我们三个都走
Which is why if one of us goes, we all go.
嗯 好吧 那你们都...
Huh. Okay. Then you're all...
也就是说那只是个假设
Which is why that was just a hypothetical.
这个词用得好 Mike
That's the exact word that I'd use for this, Mike.
悲 剧
High-pathetic.
Dan 你是不是要告诉我 如果我要炒这俩白痴里的一个
Dan, are you telling me that if I fired either one of these bozos,
你就辞职? 不会 女士
- you would have resigned? - No, ma'am.
我从未承认这个方案
I was never really committed to this as an idea.
是吧
Right, yeah.
这是个巨大的错误 可以说是个笑话
This was a big mistake. Kind of a joke, really.
谢谢你们啊
Thanks, guys.
Mike 你都说不清自杀合约是什么
Mike, you can't even announce a suicide pact correctly.
因为Dan说得太快了
Dan folded pretty quick.
进来
Yeah, come in.
哦 Gary 我需要雅维 (解热镇痛药)
Oh, Gary, I need advil.
我的头大片大片地疼
I've got a headache the size of Nebraska.
我可能做不了了 女士 这是什么
- I'm afraid I can't do that, ma'am. - What is this?
我爱生活 更热爱这份工作
I have loved this job more than I've loved life itself.
嗯 因为它就等同于我的生活
- Uh-huh. - Well, equally, 'cause it's been my life.
我对你的感情... 好了
And my feelings for you... - Okay.
Gary 这是什么
Gary, what is this?
是我的辞呈
It's my letter of resignation.
Gary 别这样
Okay, Gary, come on.
就因为你戴着工作证去药店?
Is this because your pass was seen at the drugstore?
你知道了? 所以怀孕的事才会被流出去?
you knew? - is that How The pregnancy story got out?
我说真的 我不会放走
I mean, seriously. I am not gonna let go
这个核心群里面
the one person in this core group
唯一个能他妈帮我做点事的人
that actually gives a shit about me.
好了 Gary 冷静点 我说...
Okay, Gary, get a hold of yourself. I mean, ser...
他今天帮我甩了Ted 顺便提下 谢谢你为我做了这事
Who dumped Ted for me today. Thank you, by the way, for doing that.
你真好 感谢你
- It was really nice of you. - You're welcome. - I appreciate that.
我的天 辞职必须拒绝
My God, resignation completely rejected, all right?
你可以帮我拿些布洛芬吗 我是你的磐石
- Would you please get me some ibuprofen? - I'm your rock.
好 但我想要布洛芬 好的
- Okay, but I need ibuprofen. - Okay.
好了 自杀合约言论中止
All right, suicide pact finished, okay?
你们可以出去了 好
you Can Get out. - Okay.
除了你 Ame
Uh, except you, Ame.
女士? 嗯
- Ma'am? - Mm-hmm.
坐 拜托您 必须...
- Just have a seat. - Please, you have to...
Amy 就坐下 好吗 就坐下
Amy, just sit down, okay? Just sit down.
我们要拿你怎么办呢
Um, what are we gonna do with you?
这是什么意思
What does that mean?
你应该知道我什么意思吧
I think you kind of know what it means, right?
我们要怎么解决这个问题
How are we gonna fix this?
好...
Okay, um...
呃 好
Um, okay, okay.
我们可以写篇关于失去宝宝的文章
We could do a piece
发表在一本有同情心的女性杂志上
in a sympathetic women's magazine about the loss of the baby.
争取些时间和信誉回来
Buy you some time and some goodwill.
不行 你是对的 不能这么做
No, you're right. We can't do that.
Um...
要不然...
So why don't...
就说我们在你怀孕期间
we say some of us mishandled things
做错了事?
because you were pregnant?
我是说...不 不 这主意不好
I mean... no, no. No, stupid idea.
好吧
Okay.
或者我们...
Or, we...
可以说
Could say
验孕棒是买给我的
the pregnancy test was for me.
哦 你的意思是 这就可以作为 你调走那个特工的原因?
Oh, you mean that would be why you reassigned the secret service guy?
因为你压力太大
'Cause you were feeling too much pressure.
有了小孩 之类的?
Baby on board. That kind of thing?
你是这个意思吗
Is that what you mean?
对 我们可以这么说
Yeah, we could mention that.
好 终于像以前的Amy在讲话了
Okay, well, it's like the old Amy talking there.
我是说 我不能告诉你怎么做
I mean, I can't tell you what to do.
这是私事
It's kind of a personal thing.
但你在想事情了 这是个好消息
But it's really good to hear you're thinking.
我要去拿点什么来止头痛
I need something for my head.
外边流言满天飞
There have been rumors flying around
说副总统办公室有人怀孕了
about a pregnancy in the vice president's office.
对 我听说了 是啊
- Yeah, I had heard. - Yeah, well,
孩子是我的
the baby was mine.
是你的?
Was yours?
对 我流产了
Yes, I had a miscarriage.
哦 我很抱歉 嗯
- Oh, I'm so sorry. - Mmm.
就是想解释下当时的状态
I just wanted to explain the state of mind I was in
所以我才调走了Collins先生
when I made the decision to reassign Mr. Collins.
这样 敲 敲 敲
I see. - Knockity Knock Knock knock.
Janet 嘿 我不知道你也在
Janet, hey. I didn't know you were here.
嘿 Amers 我们要去吃松饼
Hey, Amers, going on a muffin run.
蓝莓麦麸松饼感兴趣吗
Can I interest you in a blueberry bran muffin?
有人爱吗 我不吃 你呢
- Anybody? - I couldn't. Do you?
我不用 谢谢 没事
- No, I'm fine. Thanks. - Okay. No problem.
我退下了 一会儿看你
I will stand down. Peep you later.
什么 一会儿看你
What? - Peep you later.
好 谢谢 Mike
Okay, thank you, Mike.
你觉得能胜任工作了?
Do you think you're ready to be back at work?
当然 当然 可以
Sure. Sure, yeah.
Hey. - Hi.
嗨 不好意思打扰了
Hi. Sorry to interrupt.
我们要从熟食店叫外卖
We're getting a little lunch from the deli.
想着你想不想吃点什么特别的
Wondered if you wanted anything special from the menu.
谢谢你 伙计
Thanks, buddy.
Dan人可好了 好不容易才有今天
Dan is so good. He's come such a long way.
你要不要Dan帮你拿点什么
Would you like Dan to get you anything?
冰茶就好
An iced tea would be great.
知道吗 听起来真妙
You know what? That sounds really good.
我也要一杯 两杯冰茶
make that two. - Two iced teas.
谢谢 哦 不要这里的
Thanks. Oh, and not from here.
去那个 差不多八个街区外那家店
From the place that we like eight blocks away.
好的
Sure, okay.
他是孩子爹吗
Is he the father?
哦 不 不
Oh, no, no.
爹 不是
Father, no.
他不行
He can't.